All living organisms on Earth are exposed to a 24-hour day-night cycle.
地球上的所有生物都处在24小时的昼夜周期之中。
This cycle is the reason why people rest at night and are active during the day.
这一周期就是人们夜间休息、白天活动的原因。
Consequently, all human body functions also follow this daily rhythm, and the timing of behaviors like exercise or food intake can significantly influence your health.
因此，人体的所有机能也都遵循这一每日节律，而运动、进食等行为的时间安排会对你的健康产生重大影响。
For example, eating at night can lead to weight gain over time because food intake at night leads to increased fat storage.
例如，夜间进食久而久之会导致体重增加，因为夜间进食会使脂肪储存增多。
Many drug targets in the body follow a 24-hour cycle, too.
体内的许多药物靶点也遵循24小时周期。
This means that the specific proteins a drug is designed to modify can react differently to the medicine over the course of a 24-hour time period.
这意味着，药物旨在改变的特定蛋白质，在24小时内的不同时段对药物的反应可能各不相同。
Because how the body responds to a drug can differ depending on the time it is taken, it logically follows that taking medicines at specific times could help increase their effectiveness and reduce unwanted side effects.
由于身体对药物的反应可能因服药时间不同而有所差异，由此可以合理推断，在特定时间服药可能有助于提高药效、减少不良副作用。
When doctors prescribe medicine for people, they rarely consider the best time to take it.
医生给人开药时，很少考虑最佳服药时间。
There are two main reasons for that oversight.
这一疏忽主要有两个原因。
First, many physicians are not aware that some drugs work better during a specific time of the day.
第一，许多医生并不知道，有些药物在一天中的特定时段效果更好。
And second, most drugs have not been studied for possible different effects during a 24-hour cycle.
第二，大多数药物在24小时周期中可能产生的不同效果都没有经过研究。
Therefore, patients are directed to take most drugs during the morning or evening primarily to ensure compliance.
因此，大多数药物都是让患者在早上或晚上服用，这主要是为了确保患者遵医嘱用药。
Over 30 years ago, researchers found that the cholesterol drug simvastatin is more effective at lowering cholesterol levels when taken at night rather than during the day.
30多年前，研究人员发现，降胆固醇药物辛伐他汀在夜间服用比在白天服用降胆固醇的效果更好。
This is because the liver enzyme this drug targets is more active at night.
这是因为这种药物所针对的肝酶在夜间更为活跃。
Taking medicine at the wrong time can even cause harm.
服药时间不对，甚至可能造成伤害。
My colleagues and I wondered whether midazolam, the most common sedative used in surgical procedures worldwide, might interfere with the internal clock that protects the heart at night.
我和同事们想知道，全球外科手术中最常用的镇静剂咪达唑仑是否会干扰夜间保护心脏的生物钟。
Currently, there are no guidelines regarding when midazolam should be administered.
目前，对于咪达唑仑应在何时给药，还没有任何指导原则。
More research is needed to determine the best times to administer treatments for different diseases.
需要更多的研究来确定针对不同疾病实施治疗的最佳时间。
I believe taking drug timing into account could help make treatments more effective and help more people worldwide.
我相信，把服药时间考虑在内，可能有助于让治疗更有效，帮助全球更多的人。